[
  {
    "question": "8 x 5 =",
    "correct": 40,
    "choices": [
      -60,
      40,
      33,
      -58
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "20 ÷ 2 =",
    "correct": 5,
    "choices": [
      4,
      -2,
      5,
      -4
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1 x 3 =",
    "correct": 3,
    "choices": [
      68,
      3,
      0,
      -51
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 + 1 =",
    "correct": 9,
    "choices": [
      9,
      -20,
      -19,
      -18
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "24 ÷ 7 =",
    "correct": 3,
    "choices": [
      6,
      3,
      4,
      1
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "30 ÷ 9 =",
    "correct": 6,
    "choices": [
      7,
      6,
      -3,
      4
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4 + 5 =",
    "correct": 9,
    "choices": [
      9,
      -12,
      -19,
      19
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 - 9 =",
    "correct": -2,
    "choices": [
      7,
      -6,
      -5,
      -2
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 - 3 =",
    "correct": 4,
    "choices": [
      5,
      -1,
      6,
      4
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 - 3 =",
    "correct": 5,
    "choices": [
      5,
      -2,
      1,
      -4
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 - 7 =",
    "correct": -1,
    "choices": [
      -1,
      9,
      -6,
      -5
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "24 ÷ 7 =",
    "correct": 6,
    "choices": [
      6,
      -3,
      7,
      -8
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 3 =",
    "correct": 27,
    "choices": [
      33,
      -36,
      27,
      -65
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 4 =",
    "correct": 8,
    "choices": [
      -77,
      8,
      79,
      18
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 + 6 =",
    "correct": 12,
    "choices": [
      12,
      -10,
      7,
      -9
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 4 =",
    "correct": 24,
    "choices": [
      24,
      -27,
      2,
      15
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "24 ÷ 8 =",
    "correct": 4,
    "choices": [
      -2,
      4,
      -7,
      -8
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1 + 8 =",
    "correct": 9,
    "choices": [
      -4,
      -13,
      9,
      -14
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 5 =",
    "correct": 30,
    "choices": [
      -37,
      30,
      55,
      -77
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2 + 8 =",
    "correct": 10,
    "choices": [
      14,
      10,
      -1,
      3
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5 - 4 =",
    "correct": 1,
    "choices": [
      7,
      4,
      1,
      -6
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 8 =",
    "correct": 48,
    "choices": [
      69,
      48,
      37,
      -25
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4 + 6 =",
    "correct": 10,
    "choices": [
      10,
      5,
      -5,
      -16
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 8 =",
    "correct": 72,
    "choices": [
      -49,
      -48,
      1,
      72
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "36 ÷ 4 =",
    "correct": 4,
    "choices": [
      -6,
      2,
      -9,
      4
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2 + 4 =",
    "correct": 6,
    "choices": [
      -6,
      -15,
      -7,
      6
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "48 ÷ 2 =",
    "correct": 8,
    "choices": [
      -2,
      2,
      8,
      1
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 - 7 =",
    "correct": 1,
    "choices": [
      7,
      -8,
      6,
      1
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1 + 3 =",
    "correct": 4,
    "choices": [
      -15,
      4,
      -13,
      -14
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 3 =",
    "correct": 6,
    "choices": [
      2,
      77,
      -77,
      6
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 - 9 =",
    "correct": -3,
    "choices": [
      7,
      6,
      -3,
      -10
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 + 4 =",
    "correct": 12,
    "choices": [
      13,
      9,
      -1,
      12
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2 - 9 =",
    "correct": -7,
    "choices": [
      -7,
      8,
      3,
      9
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1 x 3 =",
    "correct": 3,
    "choices": [
      76,
      -45,
      40,
      3
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2 + 4 =",
    "correct": 6,
    "choices": [
      6,
      15,
      3,
      -17
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4 + 6 =",
    "correct": 10,
    "choices": [
      -12,
      -15,
      11,
      10
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 6 =",
    "correct": 54,
    "choices": [
      54,
      8,
      30,
      -53
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 + 5 =",
    "correct": 12,
    "choices": [
      -10,
      -6,
      12,
      -7
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 ÷ 9 =",
    "correct": 6,
    "choices": [
      -7,
      -1,
      5,
      6
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 ÷ 3 =",
    "correct": 2,
    "choices": [
      -4,
      3,
      2,
      4
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2 ÷ 8 =",
    "correct": 2,
    "choices": [
      7,
      -7,
      2,
      -8
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 + 6 =",
    "correct": 12,
    "choices": [
      12,
      4,
      -12,
      -17
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 ÷ 8 =",
    "correct": 2,
    "choices": [
      2,
      -6,
      -5,
      -7
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 + 1 =",
    "correct": 9,
    "choices": [
      -3,
      19,
      -1,
      9
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3 - 5 =",
    "correct": -2,
    "choices": [
      -10,
      10,
      9,
      -2
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1 + 6 =",
    "correct": 7,
    "choices": [
      10,
      7,
      -18,
      4
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5 - 9 =",
    "correct": -4,
    "choices": [
      -4,
      10,
      4,
      0
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "72 ÷ 8 =",
    "correct": 9,
    "choices": [
      -2,
      7,
      9,
      2
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1 - 4 =",
    "correct": -3,
    "choices": [
      3,
      -3,
      -4,
      8
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 7 =",
    "correct": 49,
    "choices": [
      49,
      -33,
      -70,
      -40
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2 - 1 =",
    "correct": 1,
    "choices": [
      -6,
      1,
      -2,
      0
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3 + 4 =",
    "correct": 7,
    "choices": [
      16,
      -6,
      7,
      9
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "35 ÷ 9 =",
    "correct": 7,
    "choices": [
      7,
      1,
      -7,
      -4
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "32 ÷ 3 =",
    "correct": 4,
    "choices": [
      6,
      9,
      -5,
      4
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9 - 7 =",
    "correct": 2,
    "choices": [
      7,
      10,
      8,
      2
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 + 4 =",
    "correct": 12,
    "choices": [
      15,
      -3,
      12,
      8
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "30 ÷ 1 =",
    "correct": 5,
    "choices": [
      -5,
      -1,
      9,
      5
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 1 =",
    "correct": 8,
    "choices": [
      19,
      -41,
      3,
      8
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 2 =",
    "correct": 10,
    "choices": [
      -61,
      -71,
      10,
      68
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 + 7 =",
    "correct": 15,
    "choices": [
      14,
      -7,
      15,
      -8
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3 + 3 =",
    "correct": 6,
    "choices": [
      -1,
      6,
      11,
      -13
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5 + 6 =",
    "correct": 11,
    "choices": [
      4,
      -9,
      -1,
      11
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 9 =",
    "correct": 45,
    "choices": [
      -31,
      -19,
      -30,
      45
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4 ÷ 1 =",
    "correct": 4,
    "choices": [
      4,
      6,
      0,
      3
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 4 =",
    "correct": 28,
    "choices": [
      -68,
      9,
      28,
      -2
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1 x 4 =",
    "correct": 4,
    "choices": [
      -68,
      74,
      4,
      -60
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 + 6 =",
    "correct": 12,
    "choices": [
      12,
      2,
      -19,
      1
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 3 =",
    "correct": 12,
    "choices": [
      12,
      2,
      -15,
      -65
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4 + 9 =",
    "correct": 13,
    "choices": [
      12,
      13,
      2,
      -17
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 ÷ 7 =",
    "correct": 4,
    "choices": [
      2,
      4,
      -2,
      -3
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9 - 1 =",
    "correct": 8,
    "choices": [
      8,
      -4,
      -3,
      -2
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "45 ÷ 5 =",
    "correct": 9,
    "choices": [
      5,
      -7,
      4,
      9
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5 + 5 =",
    "correct": 10,
    "choices": [
      10,
      -10,
      -13,
      14
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 - 9 =",
    "correct": -2,
    "choices": [
      -1,
      1,
      7,
      -2
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 2 =",
    "correct": 18,
    "choices": [
      27,
      6,
      18,
      -68
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 4 =",
    "correct": 28,
    "choices": [
      -12,
      28,
      -29,
      27
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 ÷ 3 =",
    "correct": 1,
    "choices": [
      -1,
      1,
      3,
      -8
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4 + 7 =",
    "correct": 11,
    "choices": [
      -16,
      -19,
      -6,
      11
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 ÷ 2 =",
    "correct": 3,
    "choices": [
      3,
      -2,
      8,
      -4
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 3 =",
    "correct": 15,
    "choices": [
      -25,
      -57,
      15,
      -64
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 - 8 =",
    "correct": -2,
    "choices": [
      1,
      7,
      -2,
      -8
    ]
  }
]
